musiciansnetwork.com 2013-06-06

# Musicians Networks - DJ Equipment and Musical Instruments - Musicians Directory and Yellow Pages - Music Software Downloads

**Our Privacy Policy**

The given privacy policy specifies how musiciansnetwork.com respects your right to privacy and protects any information that you provide while visiting this website.

 **What information do we collect?**

Some technical information is collected automatically on each page in order to give us an idea of how people are finding our website, what technologies they are using to access it and which pages interest them. Each time a visitor loads a page from a website is counted as one 'page load'. About once a month we also collect the current set of page load information to look for trends, for example changes in the screen resolution, operating system or browser that is most often used. We take this information into account when planning for usability and accessibility in website design. We also collect information on how visitors reach our website, including search engine use, search keyword use, and links referring visitors to our website. We use this information in our search engine optimization and marketing strategies. Some examples of the information we collect and analyze include: the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your browser type and version, your operating system and screen resolution. We do not collect personally identifiable information about our visitors without their consent

**The information we collect is used to:**

 - Understand consumer's needs and provide with a better service

 - Notify consumers about updates to our Web site

 - Promote our music resources

 - Customize the website according to visitor's interests

The information collected is not shared with any other organization, nor is any information sold or bartered unless otherwise stated.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will contact you before we use your data for these new purposes to notify you of the policy change and to provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at [admin@musiciansnetwork.com](mailto:admin@musiciansnetwork.com).

**Third-Party Advertisers**

Our site includes third-party advertising and links to other websites. We do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party websites. Our advertisers will generally store cookies on visitor's computers to record information including which advertisement they followed to reach the advertiser's website, and the date when they visited. Depending on the advertiser, cookies will expire (i.e. be automatically deleted) after different lengths of time. We use Google Adsense to support our site. Ads provided by Google AdSense are targeted to be relevant to the content of the website and / or page they are on (i.e. they get the information from the website contents not the visitors themselves). Google Adsense uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of DART cookies enables it to serve ads to the users based on their visit to the current site and to other sites on the Internet. A user may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Disclaimer**

All the information published on the pages of musiciansnetwork.com is the sole responsibility of a person/organization making the posting in the corresponding website category. Any questions, complaints or claims to the information provided should be directed to the appropriate Author or Company which has published the given information, not to the staff working for musiciansnetwork.com.

**Links to Other Websites**

This site contains links to other sites. Musiciansnetwork.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of other web sites before disclosing any personal information on another site. These other sites may independently collect data, solicit personal information, or send their own cookies to you. The Company is not responsible for any use of the information including click-stream data that you may create when using such third party web sites. You should carefully review the privacy policies of these third party web sites in order to determine how they treat your personal information.

**Contact us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, you can [contact us](http://www.musiciansnetwork.com/contact.html).
